(Sheldon:)I don't know.
(Sheldon:)I was on the Pasadena Freeway,
and missed my exit...
(Sheldon:)...flew off the overpass,
and one thing led to another.
Maybe you wanna give it a rest
and try again tomorrow.
(Sheldon:)No. I quit.
[CAR CRASHES AND MAN SCREAMS
ON SIMULATOR]
[CROWD CLAMORING ON SIMULATOR]
[ANIMALS CHIRPING AND WHIMPERING
ON SIMULATOR]
Oh. The pet store?
(Sheldon:)Remind me to compliment Wolowitz
on the software. It's amazingly detailed.
So wait. You're just gonna give up?
(Sheldon:)No, I'm not giving up.
No, I never give up.
(Leonard:)So, what is it you're doing?
I'm, uh, transcending the situation.
(Sheldon:)I'm clearly too evolved for driving.
- What does that mean?
- Leonard...